我的名字是巴里·艾伦 我是世界上最快的人
My name is Barry Allen, and I am the fastest man alive.
当我还是个孩子的时候 我看见我的母亲
When I was a child, I saw my mother
- 被一种不可思议的东西杀死了 - 跑 巴里 快跑
- killed by something impossible. - Run, Barry, run!
我的父亲因为被怀疑是杀她的凶手而被关进了监狱
My father went to prison for her murder.
然后一场事故让我也变得异于常人
Then an accident made me the impossible.
对外部的世界而言 我只是一个普通的法医学家
To the outside world, I'm an ordinary forensic scientist,
但私下里我运用我超凡的速度
but secretly I use my speed
来打击犯罪并找到我一样的变异人
to fight crime and find others like me,
总有一天我会找杀死我母亲的凶手
and one day I'll find who killed my mother...
- 妈妈 - 并为我的父亲讨回公道
- Mom! - And get justice for my father.
我是 闪电侠
I am The Flash.
前情提要
Previously on The Flash...
艾瑞斯·韦斯特
Iris West.
我听说你正在写我关于我的事儿
I hear you've been writing about me.
我正在收集关于目击红色踪迹
I've been collecting internet posts
- 的网络帖子 - 宝贝 根本没什么红色踪迹
- about The Streak sightings. - Baby, there's no Streak.
我看见他了 巴里 他穿着一件红色的外衣
I saw him, Barry. He wears a red suit.
我终于知道为什么艾瑞斯正在写关于红色踪迹的事情了
I finally diagnosed why Iris is writing about The Streak.
她是为我而写的
She's doing it for me.
我会找出杀死劳拉的真凶的
I'm gonna find out who really killed Laura,
我也会把你带出这儿的
and I'm going to get you out of here.
不论红色踪迹是谁
Whoever this Streak is,
在世界上其他人信任他以前 我是不会停下的
I am not stopping until the rest of the world believes in him.
也许我们应该隔一段时间再见面了
Maybe we shouldn't see each other for a while.
为了明白我将要告诉你的事情
To understand what I'm about to tell you,
你首先要做些事情
you need to do something first.
你需要相信一些不可思议的事情
You need to believe in the impossible.
你能做到吗
Can you do that?
好的 因为我们所有人
Good, because all of us,
我们都忘记了奇迹长什么样子
we have forgotten what miracles look like.
可能是因为奇迹不怎么出现吧
Maybe because they haven't made much of an appearance lately.
我们的生活变得普普通通
Our lives have become ordinary,
但是确实存在一些真正超凡的人
but there is someone out there who is truly extraordinary.
我不知道你从哪儿来
I don't know where you came from.
我不知道你的名字
I don't know your name,
但是我看见你做了一些奇异的事情
but I have seen you do the impossible
保护了我所爱的城市
to protect the city I love.
所以为了我们这些信任你及你所做的事情的人
So for those of us who believe in you and what you're doing,
我只想说 谢谢你
I just want to say thank you.
嗯
Hmm.
不客气
You're welcome.
你是怎么
How did you...
- 我发布才这么一会儿 - 快速阅读
- I literally just hit send. - Speed reading.
你的声音居然能够变成这样 太神奇了
It's crazy what you can do to your voice.
你需要停止写你的博客
You need to stop writing your blog.
人们需要知道你的存在
People need to know that you exist.
你还能干什么别的吗
What else can you do?
- 这不是采访 - 拜托
- This is not an interview. - Come on.
你得告诉我一些东西
You got to give me something.
爱好啊 怪癖啊 喜欢的颜色啊什么的
Hobbies, pet peeves, favorite color?
等等 最后那一个不算
Wait, scratch that last one.
红色 废话嘛 明显的
Red, duh, obviously.
- 你没在听我说话 - 听着呢
- You're not hearing me. - My hearing is fine.
但只听我想听的
It's just selective.
我该称呼你什么
What should I call you?
什么都行 除了红色踪迹
Anything but The Streak.
好吧 你有什么建议呢
Fine. Suggestions?
你说你写我是为了给你关心的人
You said you were writing about me to bring hope
带来希望
to someone you care about.
如果你这么做会让你自己受到伤害那他会怎么想呢
How would he feel if doing that put you in harm's way?
他和我这段时间有点矛盾
He and I aren't exactly on the same page these days.
而且 你正在给很多人希望
Besides, you're giving hope to a lot of people,
所以我是为了他们才做这个的
so I'm doing this for them.
未完待续
To be continued.
- 得撤了 - 嘿
- Gotta run. - Hey!
你不能就把我丢在
You can't just leave me up...
这儿
Here.
哇
Whoa.
呜 呼 呼
Whoo-hoo-hoo!
用什么工具能够偷一辆黄色悍马
What kind of a tool steals a yellow Humvee?
用什么工具能够买一辆黄色悍马
What kind of tool buys a yellow Humvee?
后退 全部给我退后
Get these people back. I need everybody back!
孩子 闪开
Son! Out of the way!
快闪开
Out of the way!
他妈的怎么回事
What the hell?
埃迪 埃迪
Eddie! Eddie!
耶
Yeah!
出来
Step out of the vehicle!
听你的
If you say so.
啊哦
Uh-oh.
啊
Unh!
看起来你真是天生欠扁
Looks like you were born to take a beating.
闪电侠
第一季 第六集
你自己算一算
Check the math.
你的处理模型并不相互关联
Your dispersal models don't correlate.
啊 如果你考虑季节浮动作为繁殖循环的一个参数
Uh, they do if you factor in the seasonal fluctuations
他们就是相互关联的
in reproduction cycles.
我们到底在争论什么
What exactly are we debating?
巴里每天奔跑过程中
The average number of bugs
吞下的虫子的平均个数
Barry swallows in a day of running.
都有希望获诺贝尔奖了
I look forward to seeing you accept your nobel.
巴里
Barry?
巴里 你还好吗
Barry? Are you okay?
13处骨折
13 fractures.
那是个新纪录 而且还只是手
That's a new record, and that's just in your hand.
你还有脑震荡 肋骨断了三根
You also have a concussion, three cracked ribs,
脾脏淤血
and a bruised spleen.
即便是你有超能力 你也需要几个小时才能痊愈
Even with your powers, you'll need a few hours to heal.
你打在什么上面了
What exactly did you hit?
一个人
A man.
一个 大 坏人
A big, bad man.
当我打到他时 他的皮肤会改变
His skin changed when I hit him.
变成了金属
Like, it turned to metal.
有意思
Interesting.
铁人
A man of steel.
所以你是一个人去跟踪了一个铁人
So you went after a meta-human alone?
伙计 干嘛不叫我们
Dude, why didn't you call us?
我不知道他是谁
I didn't know what he was.
再说了 那是我的休息时间
Besides, I was off-duty.
嗯
Hmm.
你该庆幸他没把你打的满地找牙
You're lucky he didn't knock out your teeth.
这些可不会重新长回来
Those puppies don't grow back.
奇怪的是我感觉好像在哪见过他
The strange thing is I feel like I knew him.
你什么意思
What do you mean?
他说了一些话让我觉得很熟悉
He said something that was familiar,
但是 如果我们不阻止他 他害人的
but he's gonna hurt someone if we don't stop him.
所以 我要怎么打倒一个铁人
So how do I fight a guy that's made of steel?
我们会有办法的
We will find a way.
今晚就先歇着吧
Tonight, you heal.
好吧
Yeah.
我的房间里有灯光在闪
There was lightning in my house.
黄色和红色的光
Yellow and red lightning.
有个人在发出黄色的光 然后我就出现在大街上
There was a man in yellow, then I was on the street.
我不知道我是怎么到这里来的
I don't know how I got there.
拜托 一定要相信我
Please, you have to believe me!
嘿
Hey.
你昨晚发生了什么
What happened to you last night?
被一个变态钢铁侠打了
Got beat up by a steel-plated sociopath.
值得纪念
Good times.
- 所以是一个超能力者了 - 是啊
- So he is a meta-human? - Yeah.
看来那个粒子加速器一直在起作用啊
That particle accelerator's the gift that keeps on giving.
你还好吧
You okay?
还好吧
Relatively.
知道是谁么
Any idea who he is?
我有事 埃迪先接管这件事
Eddie's taking point while I run down a lead.
在我回来之前你得和他合作
I need you to work with him until I get back.
等等 为什么是我
Wait, why me?
因为他看到了一些神秘事件
Because he saw something impossible
他会问 我回答不了那些问题
that he's got questions about, questions that I can't answer.
也就是要我 编一些看起来高大上的东西
In other words, make up some science-y stuff
来糊弄他吗
to throw him off?
正是
Exactly.
他偷了悍马后逃逸了
He stole the Humvee and evaded capture.
很高兴你可以加入我们 艾伦先生
So pleased you could join us, Mr. Allen.
这一夜不好受吧
Rough night?
额 只有一点点啦
Uh, just a little beat, sir.
就像我说的
As I was saying,
在抢劫了3个自动取款机后又劫持了车辆
our perp yanked three ATMs after he boosted the vehicle.
自动取款机监视器拍到了他
Atm security cameras caught him on video.
我们在数据库中找到了对照
We got a hit in the database.
托尼·伍德沃德
Tony woodward.
有 暴力史 盗窃
He's got a history of violence, petty theft,
袭击前科 年少时就开始犯罪
assault, going way back to juvie.
失踪长达十个月
Dropped off the radar ten months ago.
看起来他又回来了
Looks like he's back.
增加压力导致热量产生
Increased pressure produces increased heat,
如果你不释放它 就会烧起来的
and if you don't release it, you get combustion.
我不知道你怎么能记住这些东西 巴里
I don't know how you remember all this stuff, Barry.
因为他是一个小怪物 就像他的老爸一样
Because he's a little freak, just like his old man.
不许你说我爸
Don't talk about my dad.
不然呢
Or what?
他也会杀了我么
Is he gonna murder me, too?
看起来你真是天生欠扁 艾伦
Looks like you were born to take a beating, Allen.
艾伦
Allen.
- 嘿 艾伦 - 嗨
- Hey, Allen. - Hey.
你还好吧
You okay?
哦 是的 抱歉 埃迪
Hey, yeah. Sorry, Eddie.
听着 我昨天看到了一些事
Listen, I saw something last night
我完全摸不着头脑
I just can't get my head around.
嗯
Uh-huh.
我对着那偷车贼至少开了十几枪
I fired a dozen rounds at our car thief,
但貌似都被化开了
and it was like they sparked off of him.
啊 这样啊 我是说
Huh, well, I mean,
他一定是穿着防弹衣了
he must have been wearing some kind of body armor.
你见过脸上穿防弹衣的吗
On his face?
嗯   嘿
- Um... - Hey.
巴里
Barry.
嗨 宝贝 我看见新闻了
Hi, babe, I saw the news.
- 你还好吧 - 嗯 挺好的
- Are you okay? - Yeah, I'm fine,
如果你看看信息 就能发现我到底怎么样了
which you would know if you checked your messages.
我给你发了三条
I tried you three times.
抱歉
Sorry.
我必须加班到很晚
I had to work late.
嗯,我听说红色踪影救了一个孩子
Um, so I heard that The Streak saved a kid.
有什么评论么 侦探
Any comment, detective?
我所知道的是我们的罪犯逃掉了
All I know is our perp got away,
但是巴里要帮我找到他
but Barry here is gonna help me find him.
- 是的 - 好吧
- Yeah. - Fine.
不说我也能自己找出来
I have other sources.
晚上见啦
I will see you tonight.
拜 拜
- Bye. - Bye.
你们两个是怎么回事
What is going on with you two?
你说什么
What do you mean?
没什么 都还好 就是
Nothing, it's fine. It's...
我也不知道
I don't know.
好吧
Okay.
威尔斯博士
Dr. Wells.
我猜你听说了巴里昨晚的事件
I guess you heard about Barry's incident last night.
如果你正在找他 我觉得他应该在警局
If you're looking for him I think he's at the station.
其实我来这里是为了见你
I actually came here to see you.
我需要你的帮助 解决我一个老问题
I need your help solving an old case of mine.
什么事
What case is that?
巴里妈妈的谋杀案
The murder of Barry's mother.
你小时候和你掐架的孩子 现在居然是一个势不可挡的超能力者
Your childhood nemesis is now an unstoppable meta-human.
这可真是混乱
That is seriously messed up.
小时候也有和我掐架的 莱克斯·拉·罗氏
I had a childhood nemesis. Lexi La Roche.
她曾把口香糖放在我的头发上
She used to put gum in my hair.
杰克·波克特
Jake Puckett.
如果我不让他抄我的作业
If I didn't let him copy my homework
他会把我打晕的
he'd give me a swirly.
既然我们已经证实我们都是被欺负的呆子
Now that we've established that we're all uber-nerds,
我们要怎么做呢 托尼
what are we gonna do about Tony?
很高兴你问了
Glad you asked.
我们会训练你 兄弟
We're gonna train you, man.
功夫梦型
Karate Kid style.
瞧
Behold!
我叫他 戈登
I call him Girder.
事先提醒 可不是我取的
For the record, not my idea.
战斗是物理性的
Fighting is physics.
无关力量 无关大小
It's not about strength. It's not about size.
它是关于能量和精力
It's about energy and power.
用正确的方法变换你的速度
Channel your speed the right way
你就能打倒那个臭小子了
and you can totally take this bad boy down.
现在 戈登是一个移动的目标
Now obviously your Girder is a moving target.
所以
So...
我有冰和绷带
I have ice and bandages standing by.
我很确定 我肩膀肯定脱臼了
I'm pretty sure I just dislocated my shoulder.
好吧,不说谎
Okay, not gonna lie.
时间短 但是会痛到受不了
This is gonna be quick but extremely painful.
哦 这才让人受不了 埃迪 嘿
Oh, speaking of pain. Eddie, hey.
艾伦 我们发现被偷的悍马在在弗里蒙特 劳伦斯
Allen, we found the stolen Humvee in the alley
的巷子里
at Fremont and Lawrence.
你得过来开工了
Need you down here to do your thing.
啊太棒了
Great.
很快去见你 好的
I'll see you in a sec. Okay.
好的 来吧
Okay. Let's do this.
巴里 当你说你昨晚不当班
So Barry, when you said you were off-duty last night,
你没去看艾瑞斯
you weren't visiting Iris again.
你知道的 是幌子吧
You know, in disguise?
因为这有点鲁莽而且有点奇怪
'Cause that would be reckless and a little creepy.
不
No.
好吧
Good.
艾伦 你真得买辆车了
Allen, you really need a car.
我基本靠走 好么
I usually manage on foot okay.
我们有什么收获
What do we got?
托尼·伍德沃德昨晚偷的东西
The rig Tony woodward boosted last night.
没有被偷的自动取款机的迹象
No sign of the stolen ATMs.
可能那些被他藏起来了
Probably got those where he's holed up,
所以他有一个地方可以把那些东西打开
though he's gonna have one hell of a time breaking 'em open.
我不能肯定
I wouldn't be so sure.
所以 你和艾瑞斯
So, about you and Iris...
埃迪 我们吵架了
Look, Eddie, we had a fight,
而且要我和你谈这些
and I just don't really feel comfortable
真的让我觉得很不爽
talking about it with you.
我知道了 我希望你们和好
I get that, and I get that you two go way back.
说实话 一开始我有点感到你的威胁
To be honest, I was a little threatened by you at first.
你觉得我是威胁
You were threatened by me?
是啊
Sure.
我的意思是 我看到你们两个是那么亲密
I mean, I've seen how close you two are,
但你是个好人
but you seem like a good guy,
而艾瑞斯 我只希望她能开心
and Iris, I just want her to be happy.
从我的经验 一份真正的友谊难寻
From my experience, good friends are hard to find.
探长 打扰一下
Detective. Excuse me.
先生 我们悍马的方向盘上
Sir, we ran the plates on that Humvee...
加油 巴里 你可以的
Come on, Barry! You can do it!
巴里 集中注意
Barr, focus!
我不是在嘛
I am!
孩子 孩子
Son, son, son.
不要沮丧
You're getting frustrated.
你需要学习怎么控制你的情绪
You need to learn how to control your emotions.
艾瑞斯 来这儿 宝贝儿
Iris, come here, sweetie.
你让我打一个女孩
You want me to hit a girl?
他想让你试试
He wants you to try.
放松 巴里
Relax, Barry.
她六岁开始我就教她拳击了
I've had her in gloves since she was six.
她可比看起来强多了
She's tougher than she looks.
抱歉啦 巴里
Sorry, Barry.
孩子
Son...
有时候获得胜利最好的办法不是首先出击
Sometimes the best way to win a fight is not to start one,
但如果你碰到一些
but if you do come up against somebody
如果你真的面对着一个你知道你打不过的人 就放聪明点
you know you can't beat, be smart.
用别的方法会更好
It's okay to run the other way.
好吗
All right?
你怎么想
So what do you think?
从泥巴和桶来看 他喝了个烂醉
Judging by the mud and kegs I'd say he got hammered,
偷了一辆无敌的卡车
stole a big-ass truck,
去兜风去了
and went joyriding.
我打赌桶也是偷来的
I bet the kegs are stolen, too.
生锈的铁啤酒 这该是一个在酿造厂 位于
Rusty Iron Ale, it's a micro brewed right over in...
凯斯顿 我知道这个地方
Keystone, I know the place.
- 我们去那查 - 好的
- Let's check it out. - Yeah.
巴里描述了龙卷风的红色和黄色的闪电
Barry described a tornado of red and yellow lightning
里面有一个黄色的人
inside a man in yellow.
然后 突然
Then, bam.
他就身处几条街以外的大街上了
He's blocks away on the street.
不知道他是怎么到那里的
Doesn't know how he got there.
当我赶到时 那地方全毁了
When I arrived, the place was a wreck.
诺拉·艾伦死了
Nora Allen is dead.
一刀直插心脏
Single stab wound to the heart.
亨利·艾伦满身是她的血
Henry Allen covered in her blood.
尽管所有的证据都指向亨利·艾伦有罪
And despite all the evidence that Henry Allen is guilty,
但现在你相信这个 穿黄色衣服的男人才是真凶
now you believe this... What, man in yellow is responsible?
昨天晚上 我看到巴里
Last night, I saw Barry
将一个男孩从疾驰的车轮下救出
rescue a young boy from being run over,
那看起来和巴里描述的发生在他身上的一样
and it looked exactly like what Barry described happened to him.
这让我开始思考
It got me thinking,
要是一个和巴里有一样能力的人杀了诺拉呢
what if somebody with Barry's abilities killed Nora?
你的推测中有一个缺陷 警探
There's one flaw with your theory though, detective,
所有这些都发生在14年前
and is that all of this happened 14 years ago,
这远早于
which is long before...
你的机器赋予巴里那种能量
Your machine gave Barry his powers.
是一场意外赋予他超能力
An accident gave Barry his powers.
你觉得有没有可能
Do you think it is possible
在爆炸之前就存在
that somebody with Barry's super-speed
拥有和巴里一样能力的人呢
could have existed before the explosion?
警探 作为一个科学家我相信所有可能性
Detective, I deal in probabilities as a scientist,
但在这个案子里
and in this case...
是非常不可能的
It's highly unlikely.
先生们 中城警局
Gentlemen, CCPD.
有没有可能你们的货
Any chance some of your merchandise
昨晚被偷了
was stolen last night?
不 我不觉得
No, I don't think so.
那么这个家伙呢 你们见过吗
How about this guy? You seen him?
你认识托尼 不是吗
You know Tony, don't you?
嘿
Hey.
艾伦 过来
Allen, come on!
艾伦 你还好吗
Allen, you okay?
-哦 好得不得了 -起来
- Oh, never better. - Get up.
拜托 我什么都没做
I didn't do nothing, man!
那你为什么要跑
So why'd you run?
-听我说 那是一场意外 -什么意外
- Look, it was an accident! - What was?
托尼自己掉下去的 好吗
Tony falling, okay?
但我对上帝发誓 我们没杀他
But I swear to God, we didn't kill him!
接着说
Keep talking.
大约在十多个月前 凯斯顿钢铁厂
About ten months ago, Keystone Ironworks.
老板开始裁员
Boss is handing out pink slips.
托尼收到了解雇 然后他就怒了
Tony gets his, and he just snapped.
他开始狂揍那个家伙
He started beating the crap out of the guy.
我们拉开了他 之后灯突然灭了
We pulled him off, and then the lights went out.
有一种力量涌来 然后托尼
Some kind of power surge. And then Tony
跨过了横杆 掉进了一个融化碎铁的大桶里
went over the railing right into a vat of molten scrap.
就那么消失了
Just gone.
他还活着 算你好运
Lucky for you he's still alive.
什么
What?
你是怎么跑到我们之前的
How'd you get in front of us?
抄小道
Shortcut.
我是说 你的小跟班在哪儿呢
I've been meaning to ask you, where's your shadow?
什么小跟班
What shadow?
巴里啊 他有一周都没来了
Barry. He hasn't been in all week.
在别的地方忙自己的事
Getting his fix somewhere else.
太糟了
Too bad.
他挺可爱的 我有点想念有他在的日子了
He's cute, I kind of miss having him around.
艾瑞斯 好久不见
Iris? Long time no see.
我必须得说 艾瑞斯 你看起来太美了
I got to say, Iris, you look amazing.
谢谢 托尼 嗯 你也是
Thanks, Tony. Um, you too.
哦 对 我在保持体形
Oh, yeah. I keep in shape.
我那儿有个健身房
I got a gym at my place.
一直住在凯斯顿外面 在西边
Been living out in Keystone on the West Side,
你应该 嗯 你应该有时间过来看看
and you should, uh... You should stop by sometime.
那么 嗯 你想喝点什么吗
So, uh, can I get you a drink?
不 我是来见你的
No, I came to see you.
你怎么知道我在这
How did you know I was here?
我一直在仔细研读红色踪迹的东西
I've been reading up on The Streak.
找到了你的博客
Found your little blog.
你为什么一直在写那个家伙
Why are you writing about this guy?
人们说他是个英雄
People say that he's a hero.
我说他是个懦夫
I say he's a coward,
我碰巧知道他昨晚挨打了
and I happen to know that he took a beating last night
然后就像个小姑娘似的逃跑了 你应该写写这个
and ran off like a little girl. You should write about that.
你知道
Do you have any idea
皮革男是什么
who leather boy is?
没线索
No clue.
那么 嗯 如果你想喝点什么
So, um, if you don't want a drink
我应该回去工作了
I should probably get back to work.
事实上我更喜欢为你买一杯
Actually I'd prefer to buy you a drink.
-你什么时候下班 -谢了 托尼
- What time you off? - Thanks, Tony,
但我不觉得我男朋友会赞成的
but I don't think my boyfriend would approve.
他是个警察 像我爸爸一样
He's a cop, like my dad.
我从来都没有很喜欢过警察
I never really did like cops too much.
艾瑞斯
Iris!
警报
通缉托尼·伍德沃德
嗯 他等下接我去参加警察舞会
Well he's picking me up for the policeman's ball.
站满了警察 连转身的地儿没有
Wall to wall cops. Can't swing a cat.
我该给他打个电话看看他到哪儿了
I should probably call him to see where he is...
把电话给我 艾瑞斯 现在
Give me the phone, Iris. Now!
不好意思 嗯 补偿你的损失
I'm sorry. Uh, for the damage.
我们之后再见吧
We'll pick this up some other time.
巴里 来看看这个
Barry! Check it out!
你从托尼车上扯下的碎石
The gravel you pulled from Tony's ride?
含了76.8%的赤矿铁
It contains 76.8% hematite.
与凯斯顿钢铁厂的铁矿一致
Consistent with the mines at Keystone Ironworks.
十个月前关闭的那家
Which closed down ten months ago.
那是个绝妙的藏身处
It's the perfect hideout.
巴里 你介意给我讲给这个吗
Barry, do you mind telling me about this?
我有你要找的人的信息
"I have info about someone you're looking for.
他就在这
"He was here.
你知道哪儿可以找到我
You know where to find me."
她还能对谁说呢
Now who could she be talking to?
我猜你收到我的信息了
I guess you got my message.
你还好吗
Are you okay?
警察的女儿 我能自己解决
Cop's daughter. I can handle myself.
但对这个人不行
Not with this guy.
我们还是孩子的时候我就认识他 他不想伤害我
I knew him when we were kids. He didn't want to hurt me.
他想给我留下印象
He wanted to impress me,
但他现在对你念念不忘 而且不是好事
but he is fixated on you, and not in a good way.
你知道他去哪儿了吗
Do you know where he went?
他说他在凯斯顿西面有块地儿
He said he had a place out in west Keystone.
吹嘘着那有多大 但我不知道是在哪
Bragged about how big it was, but I have no idea where.
-我知道 -等等 还有别的事
- I do. - Wait, there's something else.
他的手
His hand.
变成了铁拳
It transformed like an iron fist.
他就像你一样 不是吗
He's like you, isn't he?
对 你报道我的事招来了他
Yes, and writing about me is what brought him to you.
我知道 但或许我能和
I know, but maybe I could talk...
不 他太危险了
No! He's too dangerous.
见鬼 我的车来了
Damn, that's my ride.
艾迪坚持派人保护我
Eddie insisted on a detail.
我得 走了
I have to... Go.
巴里 回答我们 你在干什么
Barry, talk to us. What are you doing?
兄弟 别急着生气
Dude, don't run angry.
我们还不知道怎么打败他
We don't know how to defeat him yet.
这就是那个地方
This is definitely the place.
你擅自入侵了 怪胎
You're trespassing, freak!
这没地方跑了
There's nowhere left to run.
-巴里 -巴里 你在哪
- Barry? - Barry, where are you?
凯特琳 过来这
Caitlin, over here!
巴里 拜托 说句话
Barry? Please, say something!
说点什么让我们知道你没事
Say something so we know you're okay.
-哦 -把他弄出来
- Ow. - Get him out of there!
你在想些什么
What were you thinking?
你到底在想些什么
我告诉过你我们能找到一个办法
I told you that we would figure out a way
-去对付他 -我能自愈
- to deal with him. - I'll heal.
你死了就不能了
You can't heal when you're dead.
他本来能杀了你的
He could have killed you.
我知道 行了嘛 我知道
I know, all right? I know!
在过去三十六个小时里
In the past 36 hours I've had my ass
我被同一个人像个小孩似的揍了两次
handed to me twice by the guy that tortured me as a kid.
我本来能阻止他的 但我现在不能了
I couldn't stop him then, and I can't stop him now!
甚至是用我的能力 对抗他我还是无能为力
Even with my powers I'm still powerless against him.
未必
Not necessarily.
思科
Cisco?
任意一种材料
Any material,
如果被超高速的物体撞击的话都会让步的
if struck at a high enough velocity can be compromised.
我们对托尼脚印上的金属做了分析
We ran an analysis on the metal in Tony's footprint.
根据它的密度和原子结构
Based on its density and atomic structure,
如果你在合适的角度和速度
if you impact it at just the right angle,
去撞击他  你会对它造成一定程度的破坏的
at just the right speed, you could do some serious damage.
我得跑多快
How fast would I have to go?
考虑到金属的抗张强度
Factoring in the metal's tensile strength,
预估的表皮厚度 大气压和空气温度等因素
estimated dermal thickness, atmospheric pressure, air temp,
你得以大约
you'd have to hit him at approximately...
1.1马赫的速度去撞他
Mach 1.1.
你想让巴里用800迈的速度去撞个东西
You want Barry to hit something at 800 miles an hour?
确切的说是 837
837, actually.
那比音速还快
That's faster than the speed of sound.
我知道
I know.
他会造出超音波爆声
He would create a sonic boom,
就像我之前说过的 超级屌
which, as I've said before, would be awesome.
我从未跑过那么快
I've never gone that fast.
目前为止
Yet.
我简直不能相信我们在拿这个想法开玩笑
I can't believe we're actually entertaining this idea.
我是说 他需要一个从好几里外来个直线冲击
I mean, he'd need a straight shot from Miles away
对 5.3英里 理论上
yeah, 5.3 Miles, theoretically.
做得对的话 你会把他打倒
Do it right, you'll take him down.
做不好的话
Do it wrong,
你的每一根骨头都会碎的
you'll shatter every bone in your body.
巴里
Barry.
乔 我这一天已经被打击够了
Joe, I've been beaten up enough for one day.
-我得 -嘿 等等
- I gotta... - Hey, wait.
一个匿名的线索我们找到了托尼·伍德沃德的老窝
An anonymous tip led us to Tony Woodward's hideout.
那个地方已经被捣毁了 发生什么了
The place was trashed. What happened?
他出现在咖啡馆去见艾瑞斯
He shows up at Jitters to see Iris.
-我得去追他 -艾瑞斯 她在哪儿
- I had to go after him. - Iris, where is she?
她没事 她很好
She's fine, she's fine.
艾迪放了在他身边放了下眼线确保她的安全
Eddie put a detail her to be safe.
我以为我这次能解决他
I thought I could handle him this time.
我试过了
I tried.
听着 我知道这个混球让你经历了什么
Look, I know what this punk put you through,
但你不能让感情影响理智
but you can't let emotion cloud your judgment.
收费站的监视器拍到了伍德沃德
The tollbooth camera got a shot of Woodward.
偷了辆车向城外开去了
Stolen car headed out of town.
州立警方已经接管了
State police are taking over.
-我们丢了他 -别担心 艾迪
- We lost him. - Don't worry, Eddie.
他们会抓住他的
They'll get him.
我想把这个家伙打趴下
I wanted to take this guy down.
我那心是你的两倍
Not half as much as I did.
走吧 艾伦
Let's go, Allen.
去哪
Go where?
缓解下压力
Blow off some steam.
-我得揍点什么 -什么
- I need to hit something. - What?
我不认为他是要揍你
I don't think he meant hit you.
去吧
Go.
所以 我听说你和这个伍德沃德有段往事
So I heard you and this Woodward guy have a history.
嘿 艾伦
Hey, Allen.
那没事 相信我
It's okay. Trust me.
我也有被学校恶霸欺负的同样经历
I had my fair share of bullies at school.
是啊 说出来也没人会相信吧
Yeah, somehow I find that hard to believe.
我那时很矮 又胖 还是个政客的儿子
I was short, fat, and the son of a politician
我爸爸关掉了学校街区的工厂
who closed the factory in my school district,
所以不是那么受欢迎
so not so popular.
那你是怎么应对的
So what'd you do about it?
我被虐惨了
I got my ass kicked.
很惨很惨 直到我的健身教练觉得我挺可怜
A lot, until my gym coach took pity on me.
她说打架的关键是要有耐性
She said the key to fighting is patience.
内心要淡定
Here.
很多人浪费了很多力气来尽可能多出拳
A lot of guys waste energy trying to land the most punches.
其实只需要一拳 但你要让这一拳有力量
All it takes is one, but you got to make it count.
找一个焦点 试着打穿它
Choose your spot and drive through it,
打六英寸深
like it's six inches behind the target.
大力点
Harder.
再大力点
Harder!
接缝那里本来就有点开裂了
The seam was starting to split.
很高兴你愿意过来
Appreciate you coming down.
嗯 这些日子以来也很难找到
Hmm, well these days it's rare to find someone
愿意和我喝一杯的人了
happy to have a drink with me.
我们昨天的谈话让我在想
Well, our conversation yesterday got me thinking.
你说过 作为一个科学家 你寻求的是可能性
You said, as a scientist, you look for the probable?
没错
That's right.
而最近以来我们都看到了
And we both recently have seen things
被重新定义为可能的不可能事件
that have redefined what is possible.
是的 并且我们都知道
Yes, we have, and we both know
导致这些事物的直接原因
the direct cause of those things.
你的加速器爆炸
Your accelerator explosion.
新科技诞生后紧随着的就是进化性飞跃
Evolutionary leaps follow the creation of new technologies.
就是那么简单
It's that simple.
就好像吸尘机器人
Like the Roomba.
是 就好像吸尘机器人
Yes, like the Roomba.
和我说说吧
So humor me here.
什么
Hmm?
如果我们知道超能力者是被
If we know that meta-humans were created
粒子加速器创造出来的
by the particle accelerator and testimony shows
而证据又证明了超能力者可能参与了
that a meta-human may have been involved in the murder
14年前巴里·艾伦妈妈的谋杀案 在我看来
of Barry Allen's mother 14 years ago, it seems to me that...
当时肯定也有
Way back then there must have been
另一台粒子加速器
another particle accelerator.
-另一台粒子加速器 -嗯
- Another particle accelerator? - Hmm.
我能向你保证那是绝对不可能的 探长
I can assure you that's extremely unlikely, detective,
而且就算有 我也没印象在我搬来这里之前
and if they were I don't recall any dark matter lightning storms
有任何暗物质雷暴
before I moved to town.
你记得有吗
Do you?
不 不 我也不记得
No, no, I don't.
你什么时候搬来这里的 韦尔斯博士
When did you move to town, Dr. Wells?
我感觉你已经知道
Something tells me that you already know the answer
那个问题的答案了 探长
to that question, detective.
那个 帮我解决诺拉·艾伦谋杀案 的问题
This whole "Help me solve the murder of Nora Allen,"
你从没寻求过我的帮助 不是吗
you were never looking for my help, were you?
你在诺拉·艾伦被杀后的一个月就开了你的实验室
You opened your lab a month after Nora Allen's murder.
你介不介意告诉我在那之前
Would you mind telling me what you were doing
你在中城做些什么呢
in Central City before that?
我在试着重新开始
I was starting over.
重新开始什么
Starting what over?
我原本以为这只是我们两个人
Here I thought we were just two guys
愉快地喝杯小酒
having a friendly drink.
你想要答案吗 探长
You want answers, detective?
苔丝·摩根 找找她吧
Tess Morgan, look her up.
52分队 这里是调度处
Unit 52, this is dispatch.
请汇报韦斯特家的最新情况
Requesting status update on the West house.
啊
Unh!
嘿 艾瑞斯
Hey, Iris.
-挺不错嘛  艾伦 -是啊
- Nice, Allen. - Yeah.
-好的 -好
- All right. - Okay.
嘿 下次注意提高你的速度
Hey, next time work on your speed.
好的 我会尽力的
Yeah, I'll do my best.
斯旺 艾伦
Thawne, Allen.
监看乔的女儿的那支分队 他们被袭击了
The unit watching Joe's daughter, they've been attacked.
艾瑞斯失踪了
Iris is missing.
快去 行吗 我打给乔
Go, all right? I'll call Joe.
我们把冲击角度调整两度
Let's adjust the impact angle by 2 degrees,
到达838的速度
up the speed to 838.
砰
Bam.
-哎唷 -只是哎唷
- Ouch. - Ouch?
伙计们 你们在吗
Guys, you there?
在啊兄弟 怎么了
Yeah, man, what's up?
托尼带走了艾瑞斯
Tony took Iris.
我需要你们用尽一切办法帮我找到她
I need you to do whatever you can to help me find her.
好吗 卫星 监控摄像头
All right? Satellites, security cameras.
-都黑进去 -交给我们吧
- Hack 'em all. - We're on it.
出什么事了
What's wrong?
还记得这个地方吗 艾瑞斯
Remember this place, Iris?
你这是打什么主意 托尼
So what's the plan here, Tony?
你终于要去考一般教育发展考试了吗
You finally gonna go for that G.E.D?
一般教育发展考试：一种给高中没有修满学分毕业的人的特殊考试，
通过了就相当于获得高中文凭
你想要主意吗 那这个如何
You want a plan? How's this?
你常常报道红色踪迹的东西 对吗
You used to write about The Streak, right?
现在你该报道我了
Now you're gonna write about me.
你绑架了我 托尼 我为什么要那么做
You just abducted me, Tony. Why would I do that?
因为红色踪迹已经死了
Because The Streak is dead.
不
No.
被我像只小虫子一样碾死
Squashed like a little bug by me.
所以如果你不想和他同样的下场
So if you don't want the same thing to happen to you,
那你就去告诉全世界
you're gonna tell the whole world
校园里有个新的大人物
that there's a new big man on campus!
而我只是刚刚开始
And I'm just getting started.
你可以让其他人给你写啊 托尼
You could have anybody write about you, Tony.
为什么要我
Why me?
因为我喜欢你 艾瑞斯 一直都是
'Cause I like you, Iris. Always have.
你早就应该说出来
You should have said something.
你再试试这么做
You try anything like that again
你身上就不只是一个小擦伤了
and I'm gonna leave more than a bruise!
埃迪 有发现什么吗
Eddie, anything yet?
我们封锁了每条主要干道
We have roadblocks on every major artery.
各分队都在搜寻
Units are searching.
我们会找到艾瑞斯的 乔
We will find Iris, Joe.
你不会觉得他会伤害她吧
You don't think he'll hurt her, do you?
长官 长官 我们收到卡迈克尔小学的火警警报
Sir, sir, we got a fire alarm call at Carmichael Elementary.
派消防部门的人过去 我们会尽量派支援过去
Dispatch the fire department. We'll send backup when we can.
那是你和艾瑞斯上的那所小学
That's the school you and Iris went to.
-还有托尼 -快去
- And Tony. - Go.
托尼 趁事态还没恶化之前赶快自首吧
Tony, turn yourself in before things get worse.
现在还来得及
It's not too late.
不 已经太晚了
Yeah, it is.
警察们已经在四处找我了
Cops are already looking for me,
所以准备好亮出这一生的最后摊牌吧
so get ready to cover the showdown of a lifetime
因为我可不会没打过一场就束手就擒的
'cause I'm not going out without a fight.
很好 因为你刚找到了一个对手
Good, 'cause you just found one.
你就不能好好死着吗
You just won't stay dead.
来救你的小粉丝吗
Come to save your little fan girl?
这是我们之间的事
This is between us.
放她走
Let her go.
哦 我是可以 但我更愿意让她看着
Oh, I could, but I'd rather make her watch
我怎么把你的每一根骨头都打断
while I break every bone in your body.
-在这等着 -好的
- Wait here. - Okay.
太慢了 铁皮人
Too slow, tin man.
-啊 -我知道你们这种人
- Aah! - I've known guys like you.
高中时曾经叱咤风云 然后就一蹶不振了
Peaked in high school. Never got over it.
有一身蛮力又怎样 看看你
All these powers, and look at you!
从小到大 都仗势欺人
Bully then, bully now.
-他受伤了 -不要啊
- He's hurt. - No!
如果你真的面对着一个你知道你打不过的人
If you do come up against somebody you know you
就放聪明点
can't beat, be smart.
用别的方法会更好
It's okay to run the other way.
你的英雄就这样走了
There goes your hero.
他出来了
He made it out.
才没有
Barely.
他为什么停下来了
Why did he stop?
他跑开了几里远
He's miles away.
5.3公里远
5.3 miles away.
-巴里 等等 -不是吧
- Barry, wait! - No way.
他要上了
He's gonna do it!
冲啊 兄弟 冲啊
Go, man, go!
啊
Unh!
超音速旋风拳 宝贝
Supersonic punch, baby!
呼
Whoo!
好拳
Nice cross.
-是啊 我觉得我手好像折了 -噢 我的也是
- Yeah, I think I broke my hand. - Oh, me too.
嘿 这是什么
Hey! What is this?
我到底在哪里
Where the hell am I?
一个你再也伤害不到任何人的地方
Somewhere you'll never hurt anyone ever again.
你他妈以为自己是谁
Who the hell do you think you are?
你知道我是谁
You know who I am.
艾伦
Allen?
你身上发生的事情 托尼
The thing that happened to you, Tony,
发生在你身上的那件事 托尼
也发生在我身上了
it happened to me too,
它不仅仅赋予了我们能力
but it didn't just give us abilities.
还强化了我们的本性
It made us more of who we are.
你变得更强壮
You got strong.
我变得更快
I got fast.
快到足以打败你
Fast enough to beat you.
你用你的天赋来伤害别人
You used your gift to hurt people.
再也不会了
Not anymore.
艾伦
Allen.
艾伦 别把我一个人丢在这 艾伦
Allen, don't walk away from me, Allen!
嘿 快回来
Hey! Come back here!
艾伦 艾伦
Allen! Allen!
兄弟 那感觉不能再爽了
Dude, that had to feel great.
-你可不知道 -就像
- You have no idea. - Almost as good
证明我对超音速冲压的判断错误一样爽么
as proving me wrong about the supersonic punch?
事实上 这很伤人 非常
Actually, that part hurt. Like, a lot.
但我可以自己做到 不需要你们
But I couldn't have done it without you guys.
我想知道的只是 接下来我们
All I want to know is which childhood bully
要去拿下哪些童年恶霸
are we gonna take down next?
-我还是凯特琳的 -好吧 行啊
- Mine or Caitlin's? - Okay, yeah.
我投我自己 怎么了
I vote mine. What?
伙计们 这可不是玩笑话
Guys, this is not a joke.
博士
Doctor.
探长
Detective.
你来这里是想提出更多的指控吗
Are you here to make more accusations?
我是来赔罪的
I'm here to make amends.
我查了苔丝·摩根
I looked up Tess Morgan.
我很遗憾你失去了亲人
I'm sorry for your loss.
你们两个在马里兰州是研究合作伙伴
You two were research partners in Maryland?
是的 我们是 我们是
Yes, we were. We were...
像许配给对方一样许配给了工作
Married to the work as much as to each other.
在车祸后
After the car accident...
我不能继续工作了
I could not go back to the work.
不能回到实验室
Could not go back to our lab.
所以你搬到这里
So you moved here.
没有人认识我的地方
Where no one knew me.
没有人会提醒我失去了什么
Where no one could remind me of what I had lost,
还有
and, um...
我
I...
我发现这很难
I found it difficult,
重新开始
starting over,
重新建立
rebuilding,
花了我14年时间的 苔丝只需要4年
and what took me 14 years Tess could have done in 4,
相信我 她 她
believe me, she... She...
诺拉·艾伦的谋杀那时
At the time of Nora Allen's murder,
我最终创建的粒子加速器
the particle accelerator that I would eventually create
只是一种概念
was but a notion,
不太现实
much less a reality,
所以 无论是谁 或者什么东西 要为她的死负责
and so whomever or whatever is responsible for her death,
都不会是源于我或我的工作
it did not originate from me or from my work.
我很抱歉我怀疑了你
I'm sorry I doubted you,
但我仍然希望 能得到你的帮助
but I hope I can still count on your help.
你不会放弃的 是么
You don't give up, do you?
不会 直到我抓到凶手
Nope. Not till I get my man.
这是我欠巴里和亨利的
I owe that to Barry and to Henry.
巴里有你的支持 他很幸运 乔
Barry is lucky to have you on his side, Joe.
嗨
Hi.
哦 我以为是其他人
Oh, I thought that you were someone else.
乔告诉我了
So Joe told me what happened.
手怎么样了
How's the hand?
没折 算是万幸吧
Not broken, so that's something.
-我该相信  -我很抱歉我说
- I should have believed... - I'm sorry I said...
我想你了
I've missed you.
是啊 我也想你了
Yeah, I've missed you too.
当我听到托尼带走你的时候 我
When I heard Tony took you, I...
我只是 我不知道如果你发生了什么
I just... I don't know what I would do
我该怎么办
if anything happened to you.
嗯 我的守护天使会保护我
Well, my guardian angel's looking out for me.
你想出去逛逛么
Do you want to hang out and catch up?
好啊
Yeah.
我很愿意 是的
I would like that, yeah.
我保证今晚我不会谈论红色踪迹的
I promise not to talk about The Streak tonight.
不 我希望你说说
No, I want you to.
不 我是说 我想 你可以
No, I mean, I want... You can...
我想你说说
I want you to talk
任何你想要说的事
about whatever you'd want to talk about.
我知道这对你很重要
I knows important to you.
太好了 因为 不仅仅是红色踪迹
Good because it's not just The Streak.
又出现了其他像他那样的人
There are others out there that are like him.
我对这个家伙的注意已经分散了给了那个着火的人
I've gotten scattered posts about this guy that's on fire,
除了他根本烧不起来
except that he doesn't burn up.
好吧 等等 等等
Okay, so wait. Wait.
你现在想同时找到那个烧火人
You're trying to find The Burning Man now too?
是啊 为什么不 我是说 一周的时间
Yeah, why not? I mean, a lot can happen
一切都可能发生 特别是有红色踪迹的存在
in a week, especially with The Streak.
哈
Heh.
我一直在试图从他那里得到答案
I've been trying to get answers from him.
他是从哪里来的 他为什么要做那些
Where does he come from? How does he do what he does?
但他回避了一切
But he dodges everything.
特别是对于这个超级加速力量
Literally, with this super-speed power.
当他移动 巴里 你甚至看不到到他
When he moves, Barry, you don't even see him.
他来去无影 就在眨眼之间
He comes and goes in the blink of an eye,
-就在 -闪电
- in a... - Flash?
就在闪电间
In a Flash.
是啊
Yeah.
今天 我被不可思议的东西所拯救
Today, I was saved by the impossible.
一个神秘人 世上最快的人
A mystery man. The fastest man alive.
然后一个朋友给了我一个关于名字的创意
Then a friend gave me an idea for a new name,
被闪电侠拯救
而有种感觉告诉我 就是它
and something tells me it's gonna catch on.
粉丝数量